<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" version="2.0"><channel><title>There is no Third Step</title><description>This is a place for all of my stories and writing things</description><link>http://localhost:2368/</link><image><url>http://localhost:2368/favicon.png</url><title>There is no Third Step</title><link>http://localhost:2368/</link></image><generator>Ghost 1.14</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 20:29:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:2368/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>Welcome to the New There is no Third Step.</title><description>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is the second iteration of this blog the first was hosted on amazon AWS this one will be hosted using GitHub pages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no third step was created thanks to my family much like everything that i do. My brother was trying to put up a guard on&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2017/10/17/welcome-to-the-new-there-is-no-third-step/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">59e65629829afba73578a9b8</guid><dc:creator>Chris Yarland-Price</dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 19:50:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is the second iteration of this blog the first was hosted on amazon AWS this one will be hosted using GitHub pages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no third step was created thanks to my family much like everything that i do. My brother was trying to put up a guard on my grandparents bed and was explaining what to do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Step one: Put the strap under the bed, Step two: clip the strap together. There is no third step.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately for him there was a slight problem. so when i became involved all that was happening was him screaming across the bed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;There is no third step, there is no third step!&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whilst i was teaing him about it later on i started to think about that saying and the fact that in my life i sometimes needed to remember that sometimes there is no third step. Step one is to decide to do something. Step two is to actually do that thing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know that there is more to planning a project than that but it is a good reminder that you can overplan everything which was something that i tended to do at the time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks for visiting and i'll see you all soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chris&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>