<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" version="2.0"><channel><title>There is no Third Step</title><description>This is a place for all of my stories and writing things</description><link>http://localhost:2368/</link><image><url>http://localhost:2368/favicon.png</url><title>There is no Third Step</title><link>http://localhost:2368/</link></image><generator>Ghost 1.14</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 23:57:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:2368/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>DragonHeart Chapter 1</title><description>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Get up you lazy twat, there’s someone outside.” a voice snapped reverberating around my head. “Get Marcus, ……  to deeeeeeaaaaaal with it.” i replied muzzily.&lt;br&gt;
“Marcus isn’t here remember. Rather than going home to our nice warm beds you made us stick around here with you.” the voice replied.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2017/11/06/dragonheart-chapter-1/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5a00f53a3f87af06da669ec0</guid><category>Dragonheart</category><dc:creator>Chris Yarland-Price</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 23:51:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Get up you lazy twat, there’s someone outside.” a voice snapped reverberating around my head. “Get Marcus, ……  to deeeeeeaaaaaal with it.” i replied muzzily.&lt;br&gt;
“Marcus isn’t here remember. Rather than going home to our nice warm beds you made us stick around here with you.” the voice replied. I decide that the voice is female but seems to have an unnatural growling quality to it. It seems familiar, but I roar at her anyway.&lt;br&gt;
“you deal with it.” I'm slowly waking up, still groggy from the dream, I try to lift my head but realise that there appears to be something perched on it.&lt;br&gt;
“And how am i going to do that arsehole, I can’t talk to anyone but you.” I recognised that voice I was sure of it. It suddenly came to me all at once, of course I knew that voice it was Samantha, my best friend who was trapped in an animal form. The reason the voice echoed and growled was that the mental link that I had constructed was imperfect and tended to take on the attributes of the form that was worn.&lt;br&gt;
“Jeez Sam, I’m sorry. Bad dream. What’s going on with the door.” i say as i pull my head up from the desk that it had been lying on. I glanced around confused. The dingy off white wallpaper clued me into the fact that i wasn’t at home in my flat and instead was in the tiny back room of one of the safe-houses. On the desk there were three monitors, in front of them was a top of the line keyboard and mouse.&lt;br&gt;
What was i doing here? The last thing i remembered was starting to do the payroll for my company, Blackheart Security. I moved the mouse ever so slightly and the spreadsheet that i had been working on suddenly appeared, the last value that i had entered had been replaced with the letter F repeated. “Damnation and hellfire, I didn’t mean to fall asleep. I’m sorry Sam. Where’s Nate?”. I look around for her mate and failing to see him I walk out of the room into the hallway. I must remind myself that this Building needs renovating. The puce colour of the hallway suddenly making me feel sick. In front of me were the entrances to the other rooms the door to the living room was open but as I walked towards it Sam suddenly kicked off again.&lt;br&gt;
“Pix it Max, pay attention, i just told you that there is someone downstairs banging on the door. It sounds important, they seem to know you are here as well. It’s been at least 15 minutes and they are not going away.” she replied angrily. I ask her and nate to start to get ready to go and step inside the office for a few minutes.&lt;br&gt;
“Why is it that no one uses the bell, it is there for a reason, and alerts me in the office.” i ask rhetorically, as i walk down the stairs to the rhythmic banging of a fist on the door. I pull open the door with a grimace and look at the woman standing there. “Begorrah and damnation, can you not see that there is a perfectly good bell with an intercom there why the hell are you banging on the door?” I roar at her.&lt;br&gt;
“I am sorry sir but i need to speak to you face to face.” She replies remarkably politely considering how rude i had been moments earlier. The only reason that a person would be that polite to me was that they must want something.&lt;br&gt;
Not in the mood to be talking to anyone especially this early in the morning and without any breakfast. I slam the door in her face. This seems to shock her slightly as it takes about half a minute for her to start banging on the door once again. I let her until suddenly she ups the tempo and force, making the door vibrate in the frame. Now that was a hell of a feat for a human, the door was a 2 inch thick piece of solid steel with 7 anchor points and a charm against intruders. If only I could charm it to repel cold callers and anyone else that wanted to talk to me. Of course that would be illegal and also highly unethical especially considering my position. But damn if it wasn't tempting sometimes. I open the door again and roar “God dammit woman if you break my door I will be sending you a bill”.&lt;br&gt;
I take in her appearance, tall for a human, especially a woman, she must be at least 180cm. She was wearing jeans and a men's shirt, with a few buttons left loose at the top. It was a casual but business like garb. She obviously wasn’t selling me anything as otherwise she would be more dressed up. It was the angle of her body that clued me in as she relaxed her posture she had moved from a slightly side-on position to a very boxy position with her torso blocking most of the doorway which was impressive considering how slim and toned she was.&lt;br&gt;
I was looking at a policewoman, used to wearing body armour, she must be newly promoted from plodding the streets, the fighting stance indicated that she was specially trained however. “What does the Supernatural response unit want with me, detective?” I ask in a slightly bored manner. It was probably another attempt to get specialist help with one of their cases. I kept telling them that Blackheart is not an PI company but a security company, but they didn’t see the difference.&lt;br&gt;
Somewhat taken aback she looks at me in surprise. “How do you know i am a detective with the SRU?” She asks. I motion for her to enter as i turn and make my way back upstairs into the main office. I'm hungry and it's not like she could harm me in any way.  She looks through the door connecting to the downstairs area where the armory and garage is, as she follows me up the stairs. I decide to be slightly obtuse with my answer. “I have a vested interest in knowing who the local SRU are seeing as i own one of the many companies that fall under their jurisdiction.” Which was somewhat true, as a member of the otraworld and offering services for other members of such. it was somewhat surprising that I had never had any trouble with the SRU before.&lt;br&gt;
I walk into the living room to find that Sam had not moved into the office as i had asked and had instead decided to sit in the middle of the room, obviously in a mood with me. “What the fuck Max are we not good enough to sit in with you and your company now? Why don’t you just put us in cages then if you are so ashamed of us.” I smile fondly at her and decide to try and soothe her hurt feelings. “Detective i would like you to meet Sam one of my oldest friends, more of a sister to me, she is mad at me because i asked her to wait in the other room whilst we talked.” I squat down in order to look her in the eyes and apologize. The detective looks at me as if i was insane.&lt;br&gt;
Sam and Nate have been cursed by a fairy that was invited to their wedding. The fairy had been an ex of Nate’s and had taken the news of his impending nuptials quite badly. So now they were stuck in the body of animals. After years of testing and trying to cure them i had managed to create a mental link between the three of us.&lt;br&gt;
She looks on suspiciously as i walk into the kitchen and pull out a can of energy drink from the fridge. “Would you like a drink?” i ask surprising myself. I'm not normally in such a forgiving mood especially when I'm still hungry and have not had a chance to fully wake up.&lt;br&gt;
She shakes her head no as i proffer a can of Monster. “Not unless you have some coffee.” she says rather diplomatically considering my attitude so far. I surprise myself even further as i motion her towards the coffee machine that Markus had installed after I finally gave in to his demands. “If you know how to use that thing go ahead.” i say. I don’t drink tea or coffee. She brushes past me, a feat that can't be helped as the kitchen is rather small. I bristle all the same, having some woman touch me reminds me of times that are better left in the past.&lt;br&gt;
I suppose that being the size of a small car doesn’t really help. I wander back out into the living room and tell her “give me a minute to go and freshen up.”&lt;br&gt;
I walk into the front bedroom rolling my shoulders, damn I feel tight but I suppose that's what I get for sleeping in an office chair. I grab a quick shower hating the feeling of having slept in my clothes. I get changed into a new outfit out of the cupboard and notice that the only things left are a pair of jeans and my training shorts which are ripped and covered in stains. Shit that meant i would have to throw a wash on or i would end up having nothing left next time i happened to need to. Needing clothes that is it's not like I spend every night at a safe house as a matter of fact I am almost always home by 8. But getting changed here was fairly common as I tended to be quite messy and that meant that every so often I would need to change something.&lt;br&gt;
I throw the shorts on and grab a shirt which i leave unbuttoned. I grab my dirty clothes and the sack of laundry that is hanging from the door of the wardrobe and walk back into the living room.&lt;br&gt;
I gesture to the woman to sit down on either of the armchairs or at the table. Walking back into the Kitchen i throw the washing into the machine and set it up to run. As it starts to rumble i grab my drink and head back into the living room. I expected the woman to be sat at the table but she surprised me by moving to the armchairs and sitting in the one with her back to the door. “I’m surprised that you just let me in and left me in here whilst you were in another room. I guess all the stories of you being a paranoid recluse were exaggerated.” she smiles at me. I lean against the table and reach out for one of the apples that is sat in the fruit basket on it. I hold it out to her, yet another surprise as I never offer people food in my domain.&lt;br&gt;
“Not really the doors to all the other rooms are biometrically locked and all of the security runs through my office. Sam was sat in here the whole time and she would have alerted me if there had been any trouble.” i said with a hint of a smile appearing on my face.&lt;br&gt;
“And how would an otter have alerted you?” she asks, obviously fearing that i am insane.&lt;br&gt;
I explain about the curse and how Sam and Nate came to stay with me.&lt;br&gt;
“Ok and why would you have asked her to exit the room unless you had already planned to bring me up here before you even knew who i was?” not really knowing how to explain that, I segue into another easier topic.&lt;br&gt;
“ You surprised me by coming in without even ascertaining that i am the man you think i am, or that i am not going to harm you in any way.” i respond with an quirk of my eyebrow.&lt;br&gt;
“I know who you are, Mr Blackheart, i didn’t come unprepared. As to you harming me, everything that i have heard about you leads me to believe that you are an honourable man and that any person that you invite into your home would be protected by yourself until such time as they left.” She looks up from her coffee and continues “ Anyway, i have no choice except to come to you in the hopes that you would provide me with the help that i need.” I am surprised that she would state her intentions with such clarity and by the way that she was talking it sounded like she was investigating something on her own separate from the SRU.&lt;br&gt;
“So i take it from your pronouns that this investigation that you want me to help you with is not sanctioned by the SRU and that you have either only suspicions or no actual proof of wrongdoing by an otrabene”.&lt;br&gt;
She gave me an appraising glance, “No, have you heard about a downswing in violence against otraworld?” She asks me suddenly.&lt;br&gt;
“no can't say I have” I reply intrigued. Very rarely is there any sort of shift in the statistics about my people. There are always arse holes who love to deem us as nonhuman and declare that we have no more rights than animals. Violence between otraworlders is commonplace but is likely not reported to the SRU anyway.&lt;br&gt;
“Well there has been, or at least that is what the SRU has decided, but I don't think that is what's happening, it seems more like that there is a group out there that is targeting supes, people are scared and they are not reporting crimes anymore, I tried to tell my chief but the higher up’s don’t want to know.”&lt;br&gt;
I stare into her eyes now truly interested in what she is saying. Conspiracy theories always amused me. Carefully schooling my face, i ask&lt;br&gt;
“Wouldn’t that be something for the Guard to deal with?” I ask. Not that the Dragon guard would really know what to do about it.&lt;br&gt;
“why would a detective from the SRU bring such a story to me rather than going to the Commander of the guard?” I ask smugly knowing that the commander would have taken her call even if it was just to get away from the tedium of the politicians for a minute.&lt;br&gt;
I get the feeling that she was waiting for me to ask that, that feeling of being under a microscope intensifies, “I have tried getting an appointment with the Commander but it seems that he is not interested in what a newly promoted detective has to say. They sent me back this in response to the letter that i was forced to send when they ignored my phone calls and emails.” She passes me a piece of paper on the official letterhead of the office of the Commander of the Dragonguard.&lt;br&gt;
“Finally when there seemed like there was no more hope i went to see someone i trusted in the otrabene community and asked them for advice on what to do. They told me that you are close to the commander of the guard, and that you had helped out supes before. They spoke highly of your actions during the cerberus incident as well as the fomori attack that took place last year.”&lt;br&gt;
I considered the revelation that she had just laid bare before me, she would be surprised at just how close to the commander she had gotten given that i had taken over the office from my grandfather close to 5 years ago. He was still the public face however so it was not surprising that she didn’t know who i was. What was surprising was that this was the first of this matter that i had heard. Up until she had walked into my office i had never heard of her nor had i heard of a possible conspiracy that would affect otraworld. That reminded me actually that i had never asked for her name.&lt;br&gt;
“What is your name detective? Why have you not introduced yourself?” She looked surprised, “I thought you knew who i was when you invited me into your Home... office. My name is Holly Neraka.”. Now that was interesting she was obviously British by birth with pale skin and the typical build of a saxon or viking warrior maiden. Yet her surname, was atypical of those found around here.&lt;br&gt;
“So detective Neraka you came to me to see if i could bypass official channels and get you into see the commander. Yet you have not told me what it is you suspect is happening.”.&lt;br&gt;
I studied the piece of paper that had been given to me, it was unsigned which was against the code of conduct. It had come out of my office however, the letterhead was perfect and the scent that was imbued into all of the official letters from my office was faint but there.&lt;br&gt;
“There has been an upswing in the number of deaths that seem to be against members of the supe community. We have found 3 murdered shifters, 2 murdered mages and a dead merfolk. There has also been multiple reports of halflings being kidnapped and never heard from again. This coincides with almost all other forms of violent crime being reduced significantly.” now that was interesting it took little to kill a shifter even mortals could do it if they had the right tools and training. Mages are just mortals with magic. But merfolk and halflings are both higher spectrum beings. It is not enough to kill their bodies as they are made of magic they can just create new ones. She continues talking as I ruminate.&lt;br&gt;
“I also heard tell that there is a new underground group that has been taking over from the gangs that have been a mainstay of the region. They have taken over so much territory and in such a small amount of time that there must be a lot of magical ability in the group. ” I am impressed at her deductive reasoning but I am sure that these incidents were between otraworlders only thus making it the dominion of the guard. I decide to see how far her convictions shall lead her to go.&lt;br&gt;
“So you have nothing but subjective rumors and dead end investigations. I know of the deaths that you speak of and there are no leads in any of those cases. The so called kidnappings are from families that have reports of abuse or domestic violence and are far more likely to be runaways. As to this so called new gang there has been no substantiated evidence that there is a new underground group that is taking over the region.” She looks down and blushes slightly, but then seems to steel herself and straightens.&lt;br&gt;
“You are not completely wrong, but i know of at least one kidnapping that is definitely not a runaway.” It suddenly started to make sense.&lt;br&gt;
“ So who is it then, your boyfriend..., girlfriend…., or a family member.” she blushes again. “One of my oldest friends has gone missing, she wouldn’t run away without telling me or at least contacting me.” I gaze at her, running through what I have gleaned from our conversation in my mind. She was a comedy of contradictions starting with her appearance, the clothes, the slim build and the muscle tone that was evident should make her into a hard looking woman who had fought to get where she was yet the smooth face, her short cropped blonde hair and freckles all gave her a pixieish look. Her nose was petite and she had gorgeous lush lips that had been accented by her lipstick. What should have made her cute and cuddly, instead she was arresting in her beauty.&lt;br&gt;
It was her mind that intrigued me, she made deductive leaps that seemed insane and yet with everything I knew made sense. On top of that she had a friend that knew enough about otraworld politics that he had guided her to me and not my grandfather. Then there was how she had discovered this house. it wasn't in my name or even the name of my business, as a matter of fact, it was registered to a man in Cyprus who had no idea he owned a flat in Newcastle.&lt;br&gt;
There was definitely something there, something that was of interest and yet I hesitated, it seemed too perfect there must be a trap here somewhere. There was this niggling feeling somewhere between my stomach and chest.&lt;br&gt;
I suddenly realised what was bothering me, and I knew then that I had to keep her close.&lt;br&gt;
I looked at her thoughtfully “Ok, you’ve persuaded me. I’ll take a look into it and get back to you.” I get up to show her out of the building. She stops me from walking through the door by blocking it with her body,I am reluctant to touch her, I feel like a kid around her one that seems to trip over his own feet and stutter. “There is absolutely no way that i am going to let you swan off and investigate this on your own, i don’t even know you. All i want is you to convince the Commander to meet with me and let me explain my case to him.” She looks up at me ferociously and her eyes flash with a tinge of violet. That was odd she smelled human but eyes changing colour was a trait that was solely otraworld.&lt;br&gt;
Finally i relent and start to get ready to head out. Walking out of the living room and turning into the office I ask over my shoulder&lt;br&gt;
“How did you get here?”&lt;br&gt;
“ I drove,” she replies. Popping her head around the door to look on as i grab my bag and all the assorted shit that i apparently have to carry around on a day to day basis.&lt;br&gt;
“In a car?” I ask. As she nods the affirmative I ask Sam to go and get nate and meet us by the front door. “Good, you can drive then, I’m not sure we would all fit on mine.” I introduce her to nate who was for some reason in the bathroom the whole time and shut and lock the front door. I gesture to Holly to take the lead as Nate follows her. She looks at my bike which is sat in the front garden.&lt;br&gt;
“No i’m pretty sure we wouldn’t. How the hell do you fit the 3 of you onto a bike?” She asks. silently adding, especially as one of you is obviously a walking mountain, and the others are an otter and a silverback gorilla. As I start to explain that after much trial and error i had managed to loosen the curse placed on Sam and Nate in order to allow them to change shape. There is a growl from the apricot tree in my neighbours garden. I focus on it as i expound on my friend's plight and how they started off with Sam as a rat and Nate as an eagle which had caused some problems whilst they both had trouble controlling the animal consciousnesses. It took an outrageously long time in order for me to loosen the curse to the point where they could shift into different animals in the same genus culminating at where we are today, they can shift into all the different animals in the world but never the same two, never human or otra world species. And never ones that could crossbreed. We had tried that at one point which had trapped nate in the body of a horse for around 10 years at the end of World war two.&lt;br&gt;
“Why are you bothering with this woman? She has delusions of grandeur and can’t stand the thought of someone being more able to solve this mystery.” Sam's voice snakes through my head like a whisper. “Nate agrees with me don’t you Nate.”&lt;br&gt;
Nate had a tendency to ignore me and Sam for the most part. We tended to bicker much like we had when growing up. In my opinion he wasn’t dealing with having been cursed in a good manner. He took all of the blame on himself and was slowly retreating from his humanity. Which seeing as he was half goblin had already been circumspect.&lt;br&gt;
“Huh, oh whatever is fine by me. Just find me someone to punch today, Ok.” he mutters. Shit he isn’t even listening to our conversations anymore. I wish i could open up the neural network that i had established in order to be able to speak with them. Nate needed a friend, someone who understood him before the transformation to remind him of the life and person that he was. The problem was that his family had forsaken him for marrying someone they saw as unfit and he refused to contact any of his old friends in case they thought less of him for relying on me.&lt;br&gt;
Putting the thought of Nate’s odd behaviour behind me, i focused on what is hiding in the bushes.&lt;br&gt;
“Nate, my friend i just might be able to satisfy your urges. 10’o Clock under the gooseberry bush there appears to be an imp spying on us. Grab him for me would you.”&lt;br&gt;
I continue to explain as Nate sides over to where the neighbours garden joins this one and suddenly jumps straight through the fence in order to grab our spy. “dammit Nate did you have to break the fence?” I ask as he holds the creature up by the feet. It was obviously some form of gremlin with the big ears and tiny stature. It's teeth were all canines, and it was bright yellow, why anyone would use it as a spy was beyond me until Holly asks. “where the hell did that come from?” it must have some form of rudimentary cloaking. Enough that the detective couldn't see through it even if I could.&lt;br&gt;
“Detective it seems that you have picked up a tail somewhere along the line. Who sent you imp?” I ask impatiently as Nate growls.&lt;br&gt;
The Imp looks at me and in the guttural speak of gnomes replies&lt;br&gt;
“no an imp. Am gnome, no one send, I follow bitch cos she smell good.” I growl low in my throat at the slur and he quakes in fear.&lt;br&gt;
“what was that? What did he say?” Holly asks quickly. Suddenly out of nowhere an eagle flies down and claws notes hand, he lets go and the imp grabs on to the eagles talon. “hah, you mad Bro, rodolfo is my bouy.”. With that he flies off into the horizon. Well detective it looks like someone thinks you might be onto something.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>DragonHeart Prologue</title><description>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;p&gt;He looked into the reflection of his face in the water of the fountain. A young boy stared back at him, he was about 12 years old, short black hair and pure black eyes. His cheekbones were high and predominant and his eyes were like a reptile’s, cold, hard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2017/11/06/dragonheart-prologue/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5a00f4783f87af06da669ebd</guid><category>Dragonheart</category><dc:creator>Chris Yarland-Price</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 23:47:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;p&gt;He looked into the reflection of his face in the water of the fountain. A young boy stared back at him, he was about 12 years old, short black hair and pure black eyes. His cheekbones were high and predominant and his eyes were like a reptile’s, cold, hard and unresponsive. “No, No this can’t be happening again.” he states. He turns around and the pure blue surrounding him transforms into the center of the small town that he had left so many years ago. The bakery on one side of him and the Tabac on the other.The town hall not 50 meters away.&lt;br&gt;
It is a swelteringly hot day at least 32 degrees, dry with a light breeze just enough to cool the light of sweat that was running down his brow. He was tiny for his age barely over a meter tall and painfully skinny. It didn't matter how much he ate or worked out he was always petite almost dainty. He hated the way everyone pitied him for it, just because he was smaller didn't mean that he was broken.&lt;br&gt;
He hears laughing and as he turns he sees a small smiling girl sitting in the doorway behind him. “Come on Maxie” she cries as she leaps up and starts running down the street, her long red hair bouncing as she moves. “Let’s go see your grandad.” “Hold on Princess“ he cries as he hurries to catch up. But he doesn’t move too fast. There was nothing to worry about, no one knew they were here visiting his grandparents. The village is tiny, less than a thousand people lived here and all of them served or had served in some way the royal family.&lt;br&gt;
As he rounds the corner he realises that she is not in front of him, as her new favourite game is hide and seek he assumes that she is waiting to surprise him around the next corner which is about 30 metres further up the road. “Princess, Where are you ?” he calls out in a singsong voice. “ i’m coming to get you.” as he looks around straining to see her he suddenly realizes that he can’t hear her giggling anymore.&lt;br&gt;
The princess was many things tall, powerful, beautiful, but she&lt;br&gt;
couldn’t shut up long enough to sustain a real game of hide and seek. “Chere princess ou es tu?” he cries in the language that they had to learn for this trip knowing that he always mangles it. He doesn’t have the flair for languages that she does. When he still does not hear her he starts to worry. “Princess you need to come out now. I'm not playing anymore. Where are you?” he wails. As the silence starts to surround him he realises something is wrong. “Princess, I need you to come out now” he roars in frustration. “You won the game !”.&lt;br&gt;
He starts to run through the streets cursing the buildings they all look the same.&lt;br&gt;
As a last resort he cries out “drachos!” Which is the codeword they used to signify danger and that she must obey what they say next. His head hanging low he realises just how wrong this feeling is, as if something was pulling him down closer to the ground. He grunts and tries to rise as he finds himself on the floor.&lt;br&gt;
“ah ah ah” a voice whispers in his ear, sweet like honey and so familiar. “we can’t have that now sugah can we.” As he closes his eyes for the last time he realises it has happened, they have come for her. Much earlier than was assumed and that he had failed. Failed to protect the one who held his heart. He struggles to get up, to fight and protect those that he holds dearest. He feels a fire light in his stomach and he lunges forward to grab the legs of the woman as she strides away.&lt;br&gt;
“Sugah you are becoming annoying. Don’t make me kill you.” He roars and releases the power in his gut.&lt;br&gt;
“Honey, you just aren’t old enough for this to be a fair fight. Come back in a few centuries and maybe you’ll have a chance.” the scenes start flashing before his eyes. His grandfather waking him. Explaining what had happened and starting the search.  Sending out warnings throughout the lands. His grandparents being blamed for his failure. The images speedup. growing older shunned by all those who knew what he had done. Realising that he could not stay and starting the journey that never ended, always looking for one person. That little girl with the deep red hair and those exquisite gray eyes that went violet as she got excited.&lt;br&gt;
He saw himself being flung from a mountain, face first as a boy laughs behind him. He saw friends that had no idea who or what he was.&lt;br&gt;
And then as always he saw the humvee. Walking towards it after a successful day's work. Then the scream of a rocket launcher. As he runs towards the wreckage he realises that Tony was in there and that he has to get him out. But he falls forward and his face hits a cold wet patch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Welcome to the New There is no Third Step.</title><description>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is the second iteration of this blog the first was hosted on amazon AWS this one will be hosted using GitHub pages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is currently no beta for this story, if you would like to beta this story then please send me an email on. &lt;a href="mailto:Chris.price@protonmail.com"&gt;Chris.price@protonmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/2017/10/17/welcome-to-the-new-there-is-no-third-step/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">59e65629829afba73578a9b8</guid><dc:creator>Chris Yarland-Price</dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 19:50:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;div class="kg-card-markdown"&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is the second iteration of this blog the first was hosted on amazon AWS this one will be hosted using GitHub pages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is currently no beta for this story, if you would like to beta this story then please send me an email on. &lt;a href="mailto:Chris.price@protonmail.com"&gt;Chris.price@protonmail.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no third step was created thanks to my family much like everything that i do. My brother was trying to put up a guard on my grandparents bed and was explaining what to do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Step one: Put the strap under the bed, Step two: clip the strap together. There is no third step.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately for him there was a slight problem. so when i became involved all that was happening was him screaming across the bed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;There is no third step, there is no third step!&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whilst i was teasing him about it later on i started to think about that saying and the fact that in my life i sometimes needed to remember that sometimes there is no third step. Step one is to decide to do something. Step two is to actually do that thing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know that there is more to planning a project than that but it is a good reminder that you can overplan everything which was something that i tended to do at the time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks for visiting and i'll see you all soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chris&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>